



23/1 Navlakha Main Road, Indore



+91 - 9131991448



purva.kushwaha99@gmail.com



www.purva.kushwaha.com

ABOUT ME



I'm a learning User Experience Designer, who loves building web, iPad and mobile solutions. I have designed product features and flows (from gathering requirements to prototyping) and brand websites, banners, posters, etc. Adding to this, planed out strategies for online and offline advertising elements. And, I seek my creative inspiration from mother nature.

SOCIAL





LinkedIn

purva-kushwaha-5885aa118

UX Designer

Purva Kushwaha

EXPERIENCE

Paragon Business

Solutions, Indore

2019 - 2020

Engineerbabu Pvt

Lmt, Indore

(2018 - 6 months internship)

Microsoft Student

Partner, India

(2017 - 2019)

Other Internships

UX Designer - Digivalet & CasaDigi

Digivalet is the world's first touch-based guest room experience solution where CasaDigi is for luxurious homes. Both are India's top luxurious brands where I have experienced designing user interactive features like Food and Beverages, Chatbot, etc. and worked on many internal projects like revamping Digivalet Dashboard, CasaDigi Studio, etc.

Graphic Designer

During my internship and freelancing work, I had experienced creating various advertising elements like logos for companies, job hiring posters, banners, gifs, email templates, social media promotion posts and some mock-ups for t-shirts, cups, stickers.

Indore Technical Community, Indore

am a tech-enthusiast who never gave up learning upon technologies. My passion for planning and designing products arose more after visiting the BITs Pilani summit, Rajasthan Hackathon 5.0 and joining different communities like Google Developers Group, Facebook Developers Circle, GirlScript and Women Techmakers, Indore. I have also worked as Student Ambassador with Skillenza and Progate platforms and have been Internshala Student Partner in 8.0, 9.0 and 12.0.

Affimantus Technologies, Indore (Website Development On Live Project)

L&T Electrical & Automation, Indore (IOT & Product Development Phases)

Nuclear Power Corporations Of India Ltd. (TAPS) (Setup of PPPoE Authentication Server Development Phases)

EDUCATION

Balchelor in

Engineering

2015 - 2019

School

2013 - 2015

Indore Institute of Science & Technology, Indore

In my college days, I have coordinated and organized many events like Techfects, Technical Events of Microsoft, Facebook and anchored at other cultural events like Kavi-sammelan, concert, Annual Days, etc.

- I also won Madhya Pardesh, Table Tennis, 2015.
- My research paper 'RNN Based Music Generation Paper' got selected in AICTE Conference, Japan.
- My minor project is BookFood Website (www.bookfood.dx.am), a third-party website for users and the caters and my major project was Smart Dustbin using IOT & Rasberry pi.
- I had awarded as Star Archiver in my final year.

Atomic Energy Central School No.1, Tarapur (Thane) Higher Secondary

In my school days, I was the head girl and house captain. Under my leadership, we had won many sports (Table tennis, Volleyball, athletics, etc.) and co-curricular activities (Debates, Quizzes, Paper presentations to Group dance, group songs, Flower decoration, etc.)

SKILLS & EXPERTISE

User Interface Design

User Experience Design

UX Research & Wireframing

Sketch & Adobe XD

Marvel App & Zeplin

Adobe Photoshop & Illustrator

HOBBIES & INTERESTS

Reading Books

Photography

Sketching

Travelling